* [Classic & Cool](https://showmegrantcounty.com/experiences/classic-cool/) Menu Toggle
* [Events](https://showmegrantcounty.com/events) Menu Toggle
* Places To… Menu Toggle
    * [Play](https://showmegrantcounty.com/places/play/) Menu Toggle
    * [Lodging](https://showmegrantcounty.com/places/lodging/) Menu Toggle
    * [Dining](https://showmegrantcounty.com/places/dining/) Menu Toggle
    * [Shopping](https://showmegrantcounty.com/places/shopping/) Menu Toggle
    * [Visit](https://showmegrantcounty.com/places/arts-culture-education/) Menu Toggle

[

](https://showmegrantcounty.com/)

Search for:  Search

* [Classic & Cool](#) Menu Toggle
* [Events](#) Menu Toggle
* [Places](https://showmegrantcounty.com/places/) Menu Toggle
    * [Lodging](https://showmegrantcounty.com/places/lodging/) Menu Toggle
    * [Dining](https://showmegrantcounty.com/places/dining/) Menu Toggle
    * [Shopping](https://showmegrantcounty.com/places/shopping/) Menu Toggle

[

](https://showmegrantcounty.com/)

Main Menu

* [Classic & Cool](#) Menu Toggle
* [Events](#) Menu Toggle
* [Places](https://showmegrantcounty.com/places/) Menu Toggle
    * [Lodging](https://showmegrantcounty.com/places/lodging/) Menu Toggle
    * [Dining](https://showmegrantcounty.com/places/dining/) Menu Toggle
    * [Shopping](https://showmegrantcounty.com/places/shopping/) Menu Toggle

* [Classic & Cool](https://showmegrantcounty.com/experiences/classic-cool/) Menu Toggle
* [Events](https://showmegrantcounty.com/events) Menu Toggle
* Places To… Menu Toggle
    * [Play](https://showmegrantcounty.com/places/play/) Menu Toggle
    * [Lodging](https://showmegrantcounty.com/places/lodging/) Menu Toggle
    * [Dining](https://showmegrantcounty.com/places/dining/) Menu Toggle
    * [Shopping](https://showmegrantcounty.com/places/shopping/) Menu Toggle
    * [Visit](https://showmegrantcounty.com/places/arts-culture-education/) Menu Toggle

[

](https://showmegrantcounty.com/)

Search for:  Search

* [Classic & Cool](#) Menu Toggle
* [Events](#) Menu Toggle
* [Places](https://showmegrantcounty.com/places/) Menu Toggle
    * [Lodging](https://showmegrantcounty.com/places/lodging/) Menu Toggle
    * [Dining](https://showmegrantcounty.com/places/dining/) Menu Toggle
    * [Shopping](https://showmegrantcounty.com/places/shopping/) Menu Toggle

[

](https://showmegrantcounty.com/)

Main Menu

* [Classic & Cool](#) Menu Toggle
* [Events](#) Menu Toggle
* [Places](https://showmegrantcounty.com/places/) Menu Toggle
    * [Lodging](https://showmegrantcounty.com/places/lodging/) Menu Toggle
    * [Dining](https://showmegrantcounty.com/places/dining/) Menu Toggle
    * [Shopping](https://showmegrantcounty.com/places/shopping/) Menu Toggle

Privacy Policy
==============

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you visit our site, register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

* To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
* To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
* To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
* To send periodic emails The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or you may contact us at info@showmegrantcounty.com.

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then saved into our database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) may be kept on file for more than 60 days in order to contact you about future events and attractions you may be interested in.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. Do we disclose any information to outside parties? We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act) as we do not actively collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. This policy was last modified on 03/22/2011

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

P. O. Box 1327  
Marion, Indiana 46952  
United States

About Grant County
------------------

Grant County, Indiana, is home to nifty attractions, outtasight events and rebellious celebrities. Whether it’s saddle shoes, classic cars, vintage bikes, James Dean, or Garfield, we love everything classic and cool. Have a blast just 90 minutes North of Indy.

© 2024 Grant County, Indiana. All rights reserved. | Garfield © PAWS Inc. All rights reserved.

Scroll to Top
